Guide to the Alumni Records Office, Yale University, Alumni Military Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Alumni Records Office, Yale University, alumni military service records
1870-1951
RU 278
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
28
The records consist of data cards documenting the military service of Yale alumni.
Yale University. Alumni Records Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 8-B (YRG 8-B), Records on individual Yale alumni.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of data cards documenting the military service of Yale alumni.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Veterans; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University. Alumni Records Office
- Alumni military service record cards, 1870-1951; Accession 1996-A-069
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2027
  - 1870 - Kennech Ives, 1924 (Box 1)
  - Norman R. Jeffrey, 1924 - John M.K. Davis, 1929 (Box 2)
  - George W. Dean, 1929 - J. Barclay Potts, 1931 (Box 3)
  - Francis C. Power, 1931 - G. West, 1933 (Box 4)
  - Reuben Waterman, 1933 - Charles S?, 1935 (Box 5)
  - J. Stonington, 1935 - Chester Loomis, 1937 (Box 6)
  - R. Lucey, 1937 - Frederick Gleason, 1939 (Box 7)
  - G. Gadley, 1939 - Henry S. Taylor, 1940 (Box 8)
  - George, Tenor?, 1940 - Howard Carleon? 1942 (Box 9)
  - Edward Carpenter, 1942 - Leonard C. R?, Jr., 1943 (Box 10)
  - Charles Stephens, 1943 - Bruce Croumiter, Jr., 1945 (Box 11)
  - George Crossmann II, 1945 - Donald Loyal Levenworth, 1945W (Box 12)
  - Franklin E. Parker, 1946 - Charles S. Sloan, 1947 ex (Box 14)
  - Robert J. Aley, 1947 - George Prideaux, 1949 (Box 15)
  - Thomas G. Prioleau, Jr., 1949 - John W. Haines, Jr., 1950 (Box 16)
  - John S. Hansen, 1950 - Peter J. Lagemann, 1951 (Box 17)
  - David M. Lamb, 1951 - James P. McKenna, Jr., 1934S ex (Box 18)
  - Richard O. Marsh, Jr. 1934S ex - John Wallace, 1939E ex (Box 19)
  - Maurice Allen, 1940S - Theodore D. Olmstead, Jr., 1934S (Box 20)
  - Dwight Wadsworth, 1945E ex - Donald Clifford Smith, 1946S (Box 22)
  - David Smith, 1945S - Frederick E. Souncog? (Box 23)
  - Alphonse C. Soockes? - Eugene V. Zumwalz? (Box 24)
- World War II alumni and staff military service record cards, circa 1946; Accession 1997-A-029 (Box 1–24)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.